Nguyen Thap Nhat Bao

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Over 7 years of constantly deep diving in the creative working, with board skills and experiences in Communication Marketing, Partnership Development and Project Management. Looking for opportunities to maximize my potential and abilities. Which are:

- Develop a global mindset.
- Practice professional skills.
- Expand professional network.

Experience

Creative Writing (Music Production)

Freelance

Jul 2021 - Present (10 months +)

- Master creative progression.
- Strong understanding the art of leading audience's emotion.
- Practice the art of leading emotion through melody, instruments, sound and words.
- Writing a story that synchronize with requirement of music and song progression.



Music Training & Performance

English Town - Thành phố Tiếng Anh giữa lòng Sài Gòn

Nov 2018 - Jan 2020 (1 year 3 months)

- Practiced the art of charismatic communication.
- Inspired student.
- Developed creative training methods to approach students.

Project Management

Vinh Hy Shirmp Farm

Jul 2016 - Mar 2018 (1 year 9 months)

- Working with workers, manager, engineer, suppliers,...
- Negotiate commercial contracts with industry partners.
- Established working process for farm manager and workers.
- Managed the construction and purchase process.

Brand Conceptualization

Freelance

Jul 2016 - Dec 2017 (1 year 6 months)

- Get creative brief from client
- Conceptualization.
- Design implement.

- Client pitching.

Commucation Design cum Account Executive

EloQ Communications

Oct 2015 - Jun 2016 (9 months)

- Led creative apartment.
- Joined the process of brainstorming a creative plan.
- Supported team to implement client's project.
- Prospected, contacted and approached potential clients.

Partnership Development (Start-up Community Building)

HATCH! Ventures

Mar 2014 - Dec 2014 (10 months)

- Prospected, contacted and approached start-up founders/co-founders.
- Built awareness about HATCH! through networking events, social media,...
- Led and supported team to organize monthly Talk shows.
- Connected founders/co-founders to join start-up competition.
- Supported team to organize Seed Star World competition in Vietnam (HCMC).
- Supported team to organize HATCH! Battle in HCMC.
- Working with media.

Education

MPU

Comtemporary music in Writing and Production



BMG International

Applied Professional Marketing



HCM University Of Technology (HUTECH)

Bachelor of Finance and Banking



Skills

Project Management • Partnership Development • Business Development • Marketing Communications

· Creative Direction · Account Management · Art Direction · Music Production